{
"question": "一昨日",
"answer": "おととい"
},
{
"question": "テープ",
"answer": "テープ"
},
{
"question": "ストーブ",
"answer": "ストーブ"
},
{
"question": "カップ",
"answer": "カップ"
},
{
"question": "テープレコーダー",
"answer": "テープレコーダー"
},
{
"question": "ボールペン",
"answer": "ボールペン"
},
{
"question": "スプーン",
"answer": "スプーン"
},
{
"question": "スリッパ",
"answer": "スリッパ"
},
{
"question": "醤油",
"answer": "しょうゆ"
},
{
"question": "はい",
"answer": "はい"
},
{
"question": "ペット",
"answer": "ペット"
},
{
"question": "為る",
"answer": "する"
},
{
"question": "彼",
"answer": "あれ"
},
{
"question": "一日-1",
"answer": "ついたち"
},
{
"question": "三日",
"answer": "みっか"
},
{
"question": "二日",
"answer": "ふつか"
},
{
"question": "五日",
"answer": "いつか"
},
{
"question": "十日",
"answer": "とおか"
},
{
"question": "六日",
"answer": "むいか"
},
{
"question": "八日",
"answer": "ようか"
},
